let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which spell is used to  'Turn Off the Wands Light ' ?",
    answer: "Nox",
    options: [
      "Nox",
      "Duro",
      "Diffindo",
      "Locomotor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Create Pain In Victims Eyes'?",
    answer: "Conjunctivities",
    options: [
      "Mufflito",
      "Protego Horribilis",
      "Glisseo",
      "Conjunctivities"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Why is Harry so sad on the day he turns Twelve?",
    answer: "Because he hadn't heard from his best friends at Hogwarts all summer",
    options: [
      "Because he hadn't heard from his best friends at Hogwarts all summer",
      "Because his owl,Hedwig,was angrywith him",
      "Because his uncle and aunt did,t give him the broomstick he wanted",
      "Because he felt old age is aproachng too soon"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the incantation of The Cruciatus Curse?",
    answer: "Crucio!",
    options: [
      "Crucio!",
      "Confringo!",
      "Cruciatus!",
      "Cutocopra!"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is Remus Lupin's nickname on The Marauder's Map ?",
    answer: "Moony",
    options: [
      "Padfoot",
      "Prongs",
      "Wormtail",
      "Moony"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Hide a Particular Memory'?",
    answer: "Obliviate",
    options: [
      "Obliviate",
      "Locomotor Mortis",
      "Aparecium",
      "Piertotum Locomotor"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What spell did Voldemort use to Kill James and Lily Potter?",
    answer: "Avada Kedavra",
    options: [
      "Levicorpus",
      "Diminoindo",
      "Reducio",
      "Avada Kedavra"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which spell is used to 'Conjure A Positive Spirit To Defend Against Dark Creatures'?",
    answer: "Expecto Patronum",
    options: [
      "Rennervate",
      "Expecto Patronum",
      "Rictusemplra",
      "Dissendium"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who took the Sword of Gryffindor to the Forest of Dean for Harry to find?",
    answer: "Snape",
    options: [
      "Hagrid",
      "Ron",
      "Snape",
      "Dumbledore"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In what psychic medium does Proffessor Trelawney foresee Harry's Death ? ",
    answer: "Interpreting Tealeaves",
    options: [
      "Crystall-ball gazing",
      "Phrenology",
      "Palm-reading",
      "Interpreting Tealeaves"
   ]
  },
];